

CONTACT

Addres

Open gates estate, karmo, FCT Abuja.

Phone

+2347039365403

∰ Web

akinwandealameen@gmail.com

EDUCATION

August, 2021

COMPUTER ENGINEERING,

Afe Babalola University

Second Class

June, 2016

WEST AFRICAN SENIOR
SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE

Command Day Secondary School

Distinction

PRO.SKILLS

React is

Next js

Javascript

Typescript

CSS

HTML

Al-Ameen Akinwande

Software Developer

PROFILE

Akinwande Al-ameen is a fresh graduate of computer engineering who craves for an opportunity to be impactful and gain relevant experience in the IT field. I am highly efficient and an effective team player with demonstrated interests in Software Development, User Interface and User Experience design.

EXPERIENCE

January 2022- November 2022 Bluechip Technologies Limited

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

i.Enhancing applications by identifying opportunities for improvement, making recommendations and designing and implementing systems

ii.Research, design and write new software programs

iii.Write and test code, refining and rewriting it as necessary and communicate with any programmers involved in the project.

January 2022- August 2022 Oasis Management Company

IUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

i. Maintaining and improving existing codebases and peer review code changes

ii.work closely with other staff, such as project managers, graphic artists, UX designers, other developers, systems analysts and sales and marketing professionals.

May 2019- August 2019

Nigerian University Pension Management (NUPEMCO)

JUNIOR NETWORK ENGINEER

i.Establish the networking environment by designing system configuration, directing system installation and defining, documenting and enforcing system standards

ii.Maximise network performance by monitoring performance, troubleshooting network problems and outages, scheduling upgrades and collaborating with network architects on network optimization.